It is that you apply a mixture of turmeric and oil and all that to the body
to the boy first and then is applied to the girl.
So that they feel better on the body and on the face, they feel soothed down.
Its a kind of a jubilant thing, now they are in for marriage.
They are now be painted for marriage you can say.
They are not supposed to them talk to anyone.
They have to keep to themselves and to be very very quietly settled down.
Now this function has to be done.
For the girls who are to be married, will you please get up and come round here.
The girls who are to be married, all the girls
Now, this thing is a turmeric, another thing mixed together.
And this may spoil your sarees a little bit, so
Bring one towl and were very simple clothes, you see, you may just wear a saree and a blouse, you may not have the inner clothes.
You can just come down there, and someone will apply this to you, or you can sit there at one side
Then you have to go for a bath, to arrange for the bath now
Where are you?
This come this side
Now
You first go from here so we will have to apply this to the boys first.
Now those boys who are going to get married, should come forward.
With great courage.
Now all your clothes are going to be spoilt,
so best thing would be that you change your dresses
and bring a towl, and wrap it and sit down with a towel
Go go go all of you, just bring a nice big towel, so that you cover yourself. All these clothes have to be taken,
I am sorry, you have to be in your birthday suits.
This has a very secret thing you see
If the boy is suffering from any disease or anything you can see on the skin of the boy
So this system also helps a person to find out, if there is such a problem that exists.
There is quite a lot of things in it, and apart from that if he has any skin troubles, because
it is an auspicious day, if some ordinary skin trouble then also application of this soothes his skin so
it has a double purpose, but if he has some bad skin trouble I mean something comes from a very dirty disease or something
that shows on the skin, so the people know about it.
Of course these boys are healthy, but I am saying in general.
And the boys who are not getting married should go move backwards, otherwise they will also be.
Everybody must know that there clothes are going to be a little bit spoilt so be careful.
No no no you are not alright, you don't have a big thing
some big sheet or something?
Go wrap yourself completely with a sheet and come back.
All this is going to be spoilt.
Put a nice sheet around, tell them to put a big nice sheet around
Vậy bây giờ khi những người phiền nhiễu đã đi rồi, chúng ta có thể nói chuyện khác
..James con thấy ổn chứ? Ta thấy ổn, vâng. Cô ấy nói gì?
chúng ta đã nói chuyện một chút, nhưng cô ấy đã về nhà với những người khác, con hãy đến nói chuyện với Mẹ
không không không, không có gì, các con nên quấn khăn vào, cởi hết những thứ này ra
chúng ta chưa nói chuyện gì cả, những người này đã xuất hiện ..
những ông chồng rất rất, các con thấy đấy, điên rồ
Trong tiếng Marathi có một câu nói
nghĩa là .. là thứ phải được buộc ở đây
anh ta vội vàng kết hôn đến nỗi
anh ta đang buộc nó lên đến đầu gối
Bây giờ họ đang đi với bất cứ thứ gì họ có thể nắm được, chắc hẳn họ đã vội vã đến đó
tốt tốt tốt
trông giống người La Mã, Ta nghĩ vậy
Được rồi, bây giờ thì tốt rồi
cái gì vậy? ồ con phải mặc thêm gì đó nữa
con không có gì ở đây sao? quần của con sẽ bị bẩn.. con không phiền chứ?
không sao đâu, vậy thì được rồi..
hai con thật hợp nhau
Rajneesh quá thấp so với con
tốt hơn là
cô ấy nói cô ấy bối rối ... Ta nói không sao cả..
Dev... Dev?
cậu ấy đâu rồi?
Chúc mừng.. cô ấy ổn
Vậy Ta sẽ phải thông báo lễ đính hôn của
Mathuri và Dev
rất tốt .. rất tuyệt
được rồi
chúc mừng
cứ để họ làm trước
vì họ phải di chuyển, họ biết rõ hơn
Xin chào mọi người..
Tất cả các chàng trai
Phải đi tắm
trước tiên các con hãy ra biển
Tắm rửa sạch sẽ ở đó
thông báo đính hôn ..Hamy và Glenda
Hamy và Glenda
những người sắp kết hôn phải đi ra phía sau.. có nước cho họ ở đó
bây giờ từng người một, mỗi cô dâu
sẽ đến dâng quả dừa cho Shri Mataji, dâng hoa ....... dưới Chân Sen của Shri Mataji, sau đó quay trở lại
con phải buộc nó sao cho vầng trán của con
phải lộ ra, nó không được trễ xuống như vậy
những phù dâu phải xem các cô dâu...
Làm ơn buộc nó cao lên, Ta thậm chí không thể chấm tika nếu con để nó thấp như vậy
Buộc cao lên
nên chặt hơn .. vâng
trông không đẹp, nó thấp quá
rất thấp
nên cao hơn
Phải thoa chút phấn cho cô ấy
đen hết cả rồi
thoa chút phấn đi
Con là người chăm sóc cô ấy à?
Con là phù dâu của cô ấy à?
Con có phải là phù dâu của cô ấy không?
phải không?
rất đẹp